

# **FURKAN KAPUKAYA**

JUNIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

## **ABOUT**

I am a person who is open to self-development, aims to gain experience and benefit himself and the company he works for. I am a person who adapts to teamwork, is problem solving oriented, fast and does not give up, follows new technologies quickly, and tries to convey what he knows. I want to take responsibility in every field and show myself in the company where I have worked for many years.

# **EDUCATION**

## **Anatolian University**

MANAGEMENT INFORMATION SYSTEMS | 2022 - NOW

## Kirklareli University

COMPUTER PROGRAMMING | 2019 - 2021

- 3,55/4 AGNO
- Artificial Intelligence Workshop Volunteer
- I studied C#, Python, Java, PostgreSQL, PHP, HTML and CSS technologies at a basic level.

#### COMPUTER SKILLS

C# (Windows Forms - Web - Console)
.NET | .NET Core
ASP.NET (MVC - Layered Architecture)
SQL (T-SQL - Microsoft SQL Server)
HTML | CSS | BOOTSTRAP
GIT (Github)
VISUAL STUDIO | VISUAL STUDIO CODE
MICROSOFT OFFICE

**HOBBIES** 



#### **EXPERIENCES**

# Jr. Software Developer

OFMARK.COM | FEBRUARY 2022 - NOW

 Base development for Ofmark E-Commerce platform for end user and companies. I have been working with Piksel Mutfak.

#### Jr. Software Developer

PIKSEL MUTFAK | FEBRUARY 2022 - NOW

# Software Developer Intern

OMEGA BIGDATA | MARCH 2021 - JUNE 2021

- I took part in web projects created for new generation loyalty platforms for shoppers and employees.
- Developing, editing and reporting web projects.
- I used C#, ASP.NET, HTML, CSS, BOOTSTRAP and GIT technologies.

#### Volunteer

ÜNOG | JANUARY 2021

I volunteered for ÜNOG's GGJ21 event. Communicating one-on-one with the participants, etc. I completed the tasks. It was an enjoyable and educational experience.

# **PROJECTS**

Github | Youtube | Portfolio Website

## **CERTIFICATES**

Fundamentals of Digital Marketing

Version Control Systems and Portfolio | Git&Github

MVC Project Camp | PG1926 Programming Camp

Blockchain 101 | Cyber Security 101 | Online Safety Training



